<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>https://ehoefel.github.io/thecyberprophet/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 13:34:18 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ehoefel.github.io/thecyberprophet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Mind</title>
      <link>https://ehoefel.github.io/thecyberprophet/posts/mind/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 13:34:18 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ehoefel.github.io/thecyberprophet/posts/mind/</guid>
      <description>Today, I received a reply from the mental health institute inviting me for a session with a psychologist. This is something huge to me as I&amp;rsquo;ve been having some difficulties for quite a while, and it feels that I&amp;rsquo;ll finally be able to get some help.
Then, I remembered that I have this thing called a blog, which is supposed to be a space where I talk about anything I want, and I haven&amp;rsquo;t shared about my struggles yet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vectorpersonography</title>
      <link>https://ehoefel.github.io/thecyberprophet/posts/vectorpersonography/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 17:43:43 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ehoefel.github.io/thecyberprophet/posts/vectorpersonography/</guid>
      <description>Hello cyber folks! I&amp;rsquo;d like to start today&amp;rsquo;s post by saying that my holidays were great, thank you for asking. It was one of the reasons why I haven&amp;rsquo;t posted in a while, others being that my computer broke, and I had to move. But now everything is fine, and I should be able to post more frequently.
How frequently?
Well, that depends on how much time I dedicate to it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>S</title>
      <link>https://ehoefel.github.io/thecyberprophet/posts/s/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 12:09:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ehoefel.github.io/thecyberprophet/posts/s/</guid>
      <description>Hello cyber folks! I was planning on posting here last week, but my pet-drone Dilik got sick, and I got quite busy figuring out how to use the RMT (Robot Medical Toolbox). But everything is sorted out now.
Before delving into the topic of today&amp;rsquo;s post, I&amp;rsquo;d like to give space to a question I received from one of my readers:
 Hello, Cyber Prophet!
I have a very important question&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello, cyber world!</title>
      <link>https://ehoefel.github.io/thecyberprophet/posts/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 18:10:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ehoefel.github.io/thecyberprophet/posts/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>Wow, I can&amp;rsquo;t believe this actually worked! I can now talk with people from the present time!
You see, I&amp;rsquo;m from the future. We&amp;rsquo;re a few hundred years ahead in time. Fun fact: for some stupid reason, your timeline is the reference point 0 in time, which is why we call it the present time.
Damn, I&amp;rsquo;m so excited! I&amp;rsquo;d be telling all my friends right now, but I don&amp;rsquo;t have any.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://ehoefel.github.io/thecyberprophet/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ehoefel.github.io/thecyberprophet/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m the Cyber Prophet! Welcome to my website. I&amp;rsquo;m using it as a communication channel with the present time. Long story short, I&amp;rsquo;m from the future. But if you are actually interested you can check out my posts. Yeah, I write posts here. I guess this makes the website a sort of blog? I&amp;rsquo;m not sure. We have memo sploinks in the future, but those are a bit different&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
